Kevin Flynn

London, UK 07796977257 flynny85@gmail.com www.kubedev.co.uk github projects

Full Stack Web Developer (Vue / Node / Python)

A motivated and naturally effective problem solver and team player, self-taught in both Games and Web development enabling almost a 10 year career in Technical Animation in Video Games industry and 3+ year career in Responsive Web Development using Agile/Scrum methodologies across Retail Food Supply and Property industries.

Effective communication skills with a practical approach to problem solving drives my passion for project delivery whether it's the front-end or back-end implementation.

Skills, Technology & Languages

- Design, UX, Mockups, Responsive design, REST APIs, Animation (2d / 3d)
- HTML, CSS, SASS, Javascript, Python, SQL, C# (Unity3d)
- Vue, Node, Express, Django, Nginx, Unity, Docker, PHP
- Jest, Gherkin, Cypress
- TDD, Git, Agile, Scrum, Waterfall

Experience

Collectiv Food

Front-End Developer | Vue, Python

Oct 2021 - Dec 2022 London, UK

Wholesale food supplier, sustainable, customer-centric B2B food supplier 'farm to fork' service.

- Worked on 3 responsive web applications (Website, B2C and Sales/Service Portal).
- Enabled customer self-service by automating single and recurring delivery slot bookings (eliminating errors caused by manual customer service emails).
- Upgraded UI framework ANT v1.0 to v3.2 in order to take advantage of Vue 3.0 features.
- Enhanced unit and regression testing from 75% to over 90% to improve continuous delivery.
- Implemented French translations to the Website and B2C websites, adding support for future languages (multi-locale).

Address Intelligence

Front-End Developer | Vue, SASS, PHP

Oct 2019 - Oct 2021 London, UK

An end to end property digital sales mailshots service, working closely with high end estate agents.

- Worked across many services that were all tightly linked (Website, Direct Mail, Web 2 print, UI kit).
- Helped in the Direct Mail product upgrade working closely with the Back-End team from Angular/Vue to Vue 2.x.
- Maintained 1 for 1 functionality during the product upgrade.
- Created new components in a custom UI kit library requiring thorough documentation/JSDocs and testing whilst following required designs (used across multiple projects/services with no breaking changes allowed).
- Led on the Mailshot design campaign service:
 - o Learning a large codebase built using a heavy mix of PHP, SASS, Vue
 - Ensured pixel perfect prints for clients under tight deadlines
 - For this I received a recognition award 'Dev of the quarter'

Kubedev

Full Stack Web Development | Vue, React, Node

Jul 2018 - Oct 2019 London, UK

After 10 years of being a Technical Animator and building tools and ideas in Games Development I began learning Web Development using many online resources, you can see many of my projects on github. Building ideas while starting my own company.

Cube.TV 3D Animation - Contract | Python, Unity

Jan 2017 Carmarthen, UK

An exciting kids 3D TV show with an accompanying game.

- Provided technical rigging and animation for 3 characters and scene props.
- Worked closely with artists and writers over a short period.

22Cans Technical Animator | Python, Unity, C# Jul 2016 - Dec 2016 Guildford, UK

An indie games studio created by the famous Peter Molyneux.

Responsible for creating rigs and animating characters and props.

Created tooling for Art/Animation using Python and Unity.

Led discussions on idea implementation between programing/artists/animators/design departments.

If You Can Technical Animator | Python, Unity, C# May 2013 - Mar 2015 London, UK

A small mobile games studio starting a project to encourage more emotional learning in games.

Responsible for creating rigs and animating characters and props.

Created tooling for Art/Animation using Python and Unity.

Created the Art/Animation pipeline process using Python and C#.

Managed the animation team to effectively meet deadlines.

TT Fusion Animator, Technical Animator | Python Apr 2008 - Apr 2013 London, UK

A studio working on the famous Lego Games, many successful titles.

Responsible for creating rigs and animating characters and props.

Created tooling for Art/Animation using Python.

- Led the props animation for the Lego City title using a new automated technique to meet deadlines.
- Managed the small animation team to effectively meet deadlines with the props.

Animated many characters

Education **Projects**

The University of Bolton 2002 - 2006 Bolton, UK BA Graphic Design & Illustration

Minitask Git Link A simple no-nonsense task tracker

Davtrack Git Link A day journal app to help keep track of mental progress

Interests

Pomodoro Link A visually pleasing timer

Bouldering - A relaxing sport Hiking - Love exploring, especially on holidays Books - Currently reading the Secret Barrister